<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Country Profile</string>
    <string name="bangladesh"> Bangladesh </string>
    <string name="india"> India </string>
    <string name="pakistan"> Pakistan </string>
    <string name="text_pak"> Pakistan </string>
    <string name="text_bd"> Bangladesh </string>
    <string name="text_ind"> India </string>
    <string name="bd_history">
        <p align="center"><b><u> National parliament House\n\n </u></b></p>
        (Bengali: জাতীয় সংসদ ভবন Jatiyô Sôngsôd Bhôbôn) is
        the house of the Parliament of Bangladesh, located
        at Sher-e-Bangla Nagar in the Bangladeshi capital of
        Dhaka. Designed while the country was still part of
        a Pakistan by architect Louis Kahn, the complex is
        one of the largest legislative complexes in the world,
        comprising 200 acres (800,000 m²).[1]
        The building was featured prominently in the 2003 film
        My Architect,
        detailing the career and familial legacy of its architect,
        Louis Kahn. Robert McCarter, author of Louis I. Kahn,
        described the National Parliament of Bangladesh as one
            of the twentieth century's most significant buildings.</string>

    <string name="ind_history">
        <p align="center"><b><u> Taj Mahal\n</u></b></p>
        The Taj Mahal (/ˌtɑːdʒ məˈhɑːl, ˌtɑːʒ-/;[4] lit. Crown of the Palace,
        [taːdʒ ˈmɛːɦ(ə)l])[5] is an ivory-white marble mausoleum on the south
        bank of the Yamuna river in the Indian city of Agra. It was commissioned
        in 1632 by the Mughal emperor Shah Jahan (reigned from 1628 to 1658) to
        house the tomb of his favourite wife, Mumtaz Mahal; it also houses the
        tomb of Shah Jahan himself. The tomb is the centrepiece of a 17-hectare
        (42-acre) complex, which includes a mosque and a guest house, and is set
        in formal gardens bounded on three sides by a crenellated wall.
        Construction of the mausoleum was essentially completed in 1643, but
        work continued on other phases of the project for another 10 years. The
        Taj Mahal complex is believed to have been completed in its entirety in
        1653 at a cost estimated at the time to be around 32 million rupees, which
        of a board of architects led by the court architect to the emperor,
        Ustad Ahmad Lahauri.
        The Taj Mahal was designated as a UNESCO World Heritage Site in 1983 for
        being "the jewel of Muslim art in India and one of the universally admired
        masterpieces of the world's heritage". It is regarded by many as the best
        example of Mughal architecture and a symbol of India's rich history.
        The Taj Mahal attracts 7–8 million visitors a year and in 2007,
        it was declared a winner of the New7Wonders of the World (2000–2007) initiative.
    </string>

    <string name="pak_history">
        <p align="center"><b><u> Quaid-i-Azam University\n </u></b></p>
        Quaid-I-Azam University Islamabad (Urdu: جامعہ قائداعظم‎; commonly referred to as QAU),
        founded as University of Islamabad, is a public research university in Islamabad, Pakistan.[3][4]
        Founded as the University of Islamabad in 1967, it was initially dedicated to the study of
        postgraduate education but expanded through the 1980s to an interdisciplinary university
        offering undergraduate and postgraduate education.[2] The university has, as of 2015,
        grown into the largest varsity in Islamabad with a total enrollment exceeding
        13,000 students.[2] The university is on a 1700 acres (or 6.9 km²) campus on
        the foothills of the Margalla.[5]
        Divided into four faculties and nine affiliated research institutes,
        QAU is among Pakistan's largest and highest ranked public universities.
        [6][7] In 2018, it is ranked between 551-560 in the world and top 133 in Asia
        by the QS World University Rankings[8] while its regional publications ranked
        QAU among 120 in Asia in 2013.[9] The Times Higher Education World University
        Rankings ranked QAU between 401-500 globally and top 79 in Asia in its 2020 lists.[10]
        The university is nationally known for its research, technological advancement,
        and intellectual interaction with international institutes, including the United Nations,
        University of Tokyo and the ICTP.[2][11] It is one of the most popular universities in
        the country and counts several public figures and intellectuals among its current and
        former faculty, researchers, or alumni since its establishment. They include Maleeha Lodhi,
        Nasim Zehra, Shamshad Akhtar, Suhail Zubairy, Farzana Aslam, Tasneem Zehra and Salma Zahid.
        The university is currently led by Professor Muhammad Ali.
    </string>
</resources>
